[Music]
in this release we allow you to bring
your capalot extension and finally run
it in the Microsoft cloud based on our
Microsoft II resources as you approach
this PA on this journey there's a couple
of things which we would like you to be
aware from practical perspective and we
cover some of those topics today and I
hope that by the end of this video we
have a good overview what you should
start thinking of as as you practically
approaching that
pass so we'll start with our basic
introductory slide uh we have a
development tools for compilot for a
year now they're very known and well
used but what's more important this
release we finally give you ability to
run your extension in our Microsoft
cloud using our II resources I'm not
going to cover building part we have a
dedicated session for that but from a
development experience what it mean that
you can take a l latest sunbox
environment you can upload your festar
capalot extension and I just magically
run so you don't need to care about
where is your LM models how is they
deployed avability and things like that
it just kind of magically runs um on
your
behalf we don't have any special
programs anymore which we used to call
before Microsoft manage I resources and
of course we're looking forward to see
what you're going to build uh with all
that the reason why it's so important
and it's so cool because finally you and
us have a same framework and
infrastructure how do we build our
compal experiences so think about your
extension as any other Microsoft
extension which goes through our IIA
toolkit which behind the scene consumes
Some Cloud compiled Services which
finally give you access to some of our
large language
models and it's not only application
feature in fact all our platform Fork
all our agentic Frameworks we're all
leveraging the same uh infrastructure
from El ability perspective from uh
resources consumption perspective so
just great that you and us finally share
the same tool set how to build Capal
experiences okay let's become a little
bit more concrete what do we mean by
that and what is available for you as a
partner as of
today uh we talk all about as of time of
this recording um as of this wave and in
the future it'll probably evolve if you
go to open a website you have so many
models available for you and as a part
of our def tools today we give you
access to GPT for or and GPT for all
mini it's a flagship models you can use
some of them for deep reasoning you have
some more fast some smaller and actually
we're going to
cover um in which cases can use which
one but that's your building blocks what
you can what you have access toward
today if you go through our I
obstruction layer we try to keep it
simple we give you aure open AI
deployments you can just say hey give me
latest GPT for or mini or 4 all and you
just get access to them so we're trying
to abstract a lot of complexity how we
deal with different version of this
models on your behalf the first question
we usually getting but it's all good but
what about all rest models
if you just look for a last two months
Microsoft have a l announcement that a
deep seek R1 reasoning Model come to
Azure Foundry open air released a number
of all reasoning models and can we get
access to
those and the truth is of course the
whole world is experimenting with those
models right now but before we as a
business Central can give you access to
those models we need to make sure that
all the world where we have OB basic
customers and that's a lot in all Azure
regions you or we have enough capacity
of those models and once we reach this
point so we can support you in a
production then of course we'll roll out
more and more model as they come but for
now you have a couple of them which is
great so you want you to stick with
those okay we talked quickly about
models and of course when you interact
with models here write to prompts so the
first question which could come to mind
what is a good prompt
I asked uh my this morning as I Was
preparing for this talk what is a good
prompt and I response get hello you a
good prompt is something which is clear
specific provide enough of instructions
and so on so forth and you want to
provide even more details for given
creative tasks okay let's try to roll
with this uh definition and take a look
on a real example of prompt if you
watching this video you can maybe pause
it and go slowly uh yourself but imagine
for a second we have a small co-pilot
which is your AI assistant which primary
function is to assist users drafting
emails to confirm appointments and
bookings in this case you have a number
of guidelines that hey you want to
confirm a booking in a in a in a in a
special format you want to start with
greeting you want to confirm time type
of fork you want to have a special
format it should be grounded in some
kind of real business data in the
professional tone and things like that
and by the way this is a real example uh
from Microsoft work from my last summer
so imagine for a second we have a prompt
like
that having that prompt your co-pilot
response could look something like that
dear Peter I hope this email finds you
well I'm writing to confirm that we have
a booking with you scheduled on that
time we're going to do that amount that
type of work which will take in that
place and if you have any questions
reach out we're happy to assist you with
that and it's very very important in the
end of that email you have like a small
link like a maybe work order something
you can click and confirm that yes it's
a booking or appointment and you can
maybe you know make some changes to that
so again from a nice prompt which so far
follow our previous guidelines
guidelines we uh see result of compile
at work with with a email which looks
like that
so it was all great and working fine on
Friday and then over weekends as of
Monday suddenly that feature that prompt
start behave suddenly a little bit
different and the emails we start seeing
look like
that hi I just want to confirm the
appointment uh should you have any
assistance please reach out I'm here to
help regards Carin and of course you
still have this link like in the of an
email which you can kind of press and
validate that yes it's booking for you
and confirm it and so forth and so and
and so on so now I want you to make a
pause and think about so how come from
response like that to response like that
overnight and if I'll will ask you to
rate that uh confirmation email from
zero stars to five stars what would be
your
rating many people would say hey
obviously it's zero Stars it's very bad
it's kind of completely dropped in
accuracy and level of details but the
interesting news that actually it's not
that bad we will say it's like three out
of fires and when I mean by that you
still get an
email which is still confirms the
appointment it still greets the user it
has a professional tone it follows the
structure and it has a link we can
verify what need to happen I would even
argue as a SMS it can be a great email
obviously obviously there is a
significant regression a lack of details
but from a prompt perspective if you
really care look on instruction it kind
of works to what you ask it to
do it's still regress significantly and
I'll explain you what has happened but
the point is here your prom still works
suddenly a little bit different and
which is not the different from large
language model will be a very different
for you as a user because no doubt we
just lost a lot of accuracy and uh
quality in those
responses now the better news for us
that in a real life it didn't happen
because we as the engineering team who
build those feature invest a lot to our
test Automation and we had a test which
verify the expected outcome of those
emails so we had an opportunity to
detect a change update our prompts and
get back to original level of quality
and what has happened is this case
actually that we had a version update
overnight so models have versions and if
it's the same model it usually can be
another version because you know new
versions can be faster or sometimes
cheaper and so on so forth so and
because every model is not better is
different sometimes you can regress some
of your
prompts so if I ask a question what is a
good prompt not to copil it but some of
my colleagues like San lout who is like
a stuff engineering team he will tell me
Well it's not that matter that much how
good prompt is styling wise or Precision
wise but it's much more important that
you have enough of test coverage so you
can verify and make sure your prompts
will work as we migrate through version
of the model and from One models to
another
models and this is something I want you
kind of have at a takeaway as you start
looking at the presentation that the
discussion what is a good prompt is a
great discussion and of course you want
to follow latest guidelines and make it
great but it's much much more important
for practical considerations to make
sure your prompts will continue to work
as we're going to update models and
version of models is really really
critical to make sure your Capal
extension will still continue to work
successfully in Microsoft cloud and of
course testing helps to have good
prompts as we just discuss uh models
will upgrade with new features and new
improvements
the new version may work
differently the new version doesn't mean
it's better it means it's different and
it's not necessarily mean it's Backward
Compatible write your test from Day Zero
and we have a number of BC session for
this event talking about our test tool
kit our responsible a principle so go
ahead and learn how you can write tests
to protect your prompt regression to
have any good prompts super super super
super important
okay we talked a little bit about models
and what you have access to and why it's
important to have a good prompts but the
next thing you have to address as you're
trying to build your extension to run in
our cloud is how we going to deal with
Fabrications which is super super
critical in business Central domain so
let me give you an ex an example of
Fabrications what is it about and what
should we do with them so let's say we
have Anna who is a user and she ask chat
with Capal question how do I reverse a
production or a credit memo now before
you even comment that those wording
doesn't have any logical sense because
in we don't have any something called
production a create memo the co-al will
say sure you can definitely reverse a
production order credit memo by going to
this and do that which is absolutely
nonsense but the reason why behave like
that because large language models train
to response statistically basically in
the same way as the data sets they
trained on and in our documentation we
have a lot of valid cases for example
you can reverse a sales invoice by doing
blah you can reverse a purchase order by
doing blah so large language models just
copy those uh type of response if you
will because it's trying to be helpful
but it definitely lead to absolutely uh
fabricated hallucinated statements uh
which is not good for for the user and
you can say well as a user I can clearly
see it's not good but what about this
example so now we have a bob uh who is
asking a chat saying Hey how do I
release a sales order and compil say
sure to release a sales order you go to
sales order page and you press release
button and so on so
forth what's interesting about this
example that actually is correct if you
go to that page there's a button called
release however and a time we would
build it feature we had absolutely no
documentation which mentioned how to
release sales orders so this is the
example which is very deceiving the llm
gave you the right answer but by poor
chance you basically flip a coin and it
give you some English words which turn
out to be true but it has absolutely no
ground to come up with that statement in
fact if it would say I don't know it'll
be much more appropriate result so again
from giving you wrong answers to give
giving you deceiving answers and this
become even more interesting so let's
say you're building a copilot for your
customers and you want to talk about
inventory levels and you can say hey do
you have an inventory for a given
product or a given place and compal say
sure of course we have enough as then
you click a link and then it falls apart
because again large language model by
definition has absolutely no knowledge
about your inventory levels and your
product and instead of just saying I
don't know it's saying you something
and uh it's not
good the reason why it's happening and
this is super important to kind of
understand and think about that large
language models always try to predict
next words or talking and it always try
to be helpful and finish the sentence
and instead of saying I don't know or
admit lack of knowledge it will try to
continue the sentence to represent some
statistical representation of sentences
which leads to deceiving answer
and that's super critical for our world
because we want to our users take an
action with trust and maybe for Creative
domain is awesome but for business
Central domains dealing with fabrication
is a huge deal it's a priority number
one which we need to tackle so now the
question is how are we going to tackle
that there is many ways and many
techniques the simplest technique which
helps us as a Microsoft is the following
always validate l l m response so what
do you mean by that imagine you build
your prompt dialog and imagine you have
some prompt or you're asking LM
something the first thing you need to do
is to validate that the response you got
from llm is legit there's many ways how
you can do it for example if you ask
about the distance or uh numbers or
weather you need to make sure that
response is talking about that and if
it's legit you can continue your work do
some calculation do some analysis and
initially at some point give the respond
to the user but if it's not good if it's
not grounded if you have a suspicion is
hallucinating or fabricating you can as
simply as try again and sometimes you
just say try again and it will work
sometimes you need to provide much more
instructions but it's like a core idea
whenever we never surface any llm
response from a system to the user
unless we verify they're grounded and
they true and now back to our um what we
allow you to do in our Microsoft cloud
with other models you might use GPT for
or for a lot of reasoning email
classifications conversation scoring to
do the main work and you might use 40
mini as a cheaper faster model to
validate its responses and this is like
a very simple pattern and I'll show you
example of it but that's exactly how we
build majority of our features
today let's take a concrete example and
the easiest way to to illustrate this
idea is to back to our classic marketing
text feature which we all love um you
can go to the product and you can say
Hey try to generate from your marketing
text when you do
that you as a user have a number of
requirements that you say hey I would
like to generate a tagline or want to
have a like a small text paragraph and
the first thing we do behind the scene
before we show this text to the users we
will validate that those settings are
hold another example is a data so
imagine you have a product which have
multiple physical dimensions or
Properties or qualities when we generate
marketing text we are making sure that
every number if you will like a size or
width or dep depth is actually coming
from a database so we don't want to have
a marketing text where uh you know you
have different Dimensions or you have a
sales campaign I give you like a th%
discount just because LM can so we do
work to validate that the final outcome
of a generated marketing text will be
what we call grounded or have the right
data point SC and only if it has so we
show it to the
user having that small technique just to
validate llm for this particular feature
allow us to increase accuracy meaning it
works from 6 % which is like every flip
Point kind of coin time to time to very
very big numbers the work is not
stopping here but just by doing this
simple technique you get significant
significant return on investment from
something which AI a to something okay
now we can maybe take a dependency or
serious talk about the feature great
stuff it's not always as easy like that
I don't want to kind of downplay the
level of complexity for example if you
uh ask our chat about how can I do
something in our documentation like how
can I do drop shipments you have a kind
of quite Advanced Machinery behind the
scene we try to go to Microsoft learn
which kind of trusted source of
knowledge retrieve all the Articles and
we'll try to prepare for you a question
from all the Articles kind of give you
this nice nice overview to help you
however we will never show it to you
before we do what before we verify
that the answer is grounded and that
answer we prepare for you actually
answering the initial
question and only if we making sure it
does that we will show you the answer
and otherwise we can you know show you
some links something else and so on so
forth yes we pay extra time to wait for
verifications yes maybe you need to wait
extra 200 milliseconds but we need to
ensure you have this trust and and
verification ation mechanism and in some
cases it's easier in some cases it's
hard but in the same kind of fundamental
idea we verify what we ask for and if we
sure we proceed if we don't sure we do
something else we can clarify but we
need to approach situation from day Zero
super
important dealing with Fabrications
should be a number one priority as you
consider to bring copilot to your users
just to avoid lack of trust frustration
bad reputation brand damage all this bad
things always validate LM
responses learn from us from this
sessions from our base up
examples All Above is essential for
having good prompts just to have like a
practice how you ground your prompts in
reality super super
important
okay we talked about
Fabrications but the question is how can
we build co-pilots which can answer user
questions which are grounded in data so
when we ask about inventory levels we
got a right and to slow response and to
do that we can use tools tools is a
really cool concept I'll show you how it
works what it does and what is the main
intent for and to U maybe illustrate you
the idea I'm going to switch to J CH GPT
and explain how chat GPT it works and
then show you how it's apply for
business Central I'm going to chat GPT
and I'll show you first how it works
with tools and without tools so first of
all I'm going to ask a question who is
the prime minister of Canada and I
specifically given instructions don't
use tools and I press go button so
what's happening now the large language
model replying on my question based on
the knowledge it has and the time when
it was trained obviously it's not up to
date what's happening right now and it's
saying hey based on what I know is
adjusting and so on so forth now if I'll
say use
tools what will happen now you have like
a small search in web happening so large
language model knows this question is
about something actual which it doesn't
have knowledge to so it tried to reach a
for a help and it uses this web search
as a tool to maybe Refresh on Research
knowledge so now it go to the web it
found information about who the Prime
Minister which was like a recent change
of March 14 it's a mark and now you have
much more grounded and
trustful um answer compared to
fabrication saying hey this is Justin
because I just didn't know what to say
anything better so exactly same approach
we can use in business Central to make
sure we can answer the question about
business data in a trustful and reliable
way so let's see how it works imagine
you're building a calet extension to
help your users to answer a question
about orders and of course all the
information about orders is kind of
stored as a business Central so what you
you can do in your extension you can
define a tool exactly the same tool as a
web search was for chat jpt you go to
our L code you define a function or a
tool and you say hey I know everything
about orders so in this case when the
user ask what is my order status we can
call your code unit which will
responsible for that it will retrieve
all the information from database about
status delivery updates tracking and get
this data back to llm and now we can
response like hey your order is
currently out of delivery here's the new
expected date and so on soers so again
without having these tools we would
never be able to get any good response
for the users but because we can
delegate to bus to business Central to
your extension to do the work we can en
reach response with the real data let's
take another example now sometimes you
can say okay but what about if I ask for
the order I think it's delayed and I
will ask for a discount we can also
approach it in the same way we're going
to define a number of tools a number of
code units a number of helpers who can
help you to do different things for
example you have a helper who knows
everything about order status or you
have a helper which can help you to
retrieve product details about prodct
product or you have a helper based on
API maybe which allow you to apply the
discounts so in this case when you run
this prompt to large language model
large language model can detect tools
defined in your extension and call them
where it's applicable and basically use
it information and to provide responses
like that yes your order is
unfortunately delayed we very sorry
about that and yes because of your
business logic we did appli a discount
for you for your order sorry for
inconvenience so tools allow you to have
this verified way to get a data inject a
real-time data and avoid fabrication and
hallucination in the real
world now what usually happen this point
of time people saying wait a minute do I
have a power now so what about if I ask
about the order and I ask for Discount
and I ask a book a meeting and I ask a
check a stock price and so on so on so
forth couldn't I just go to my extension
and add a lot of functions functions
which can do all thing in the world you
know get a reports schedule meetings
analyze customer sentiment I basically
Define as much action tools which
describe my extension and then just ask
km to deal with all of that and the
truth is at this point of time what will
happen is that it'll basically stop
working so the concept is great and it
work great but at some at some point of
time if you have too much it will just
stop working
reliably now what I want you to be cous
and be super aware if you go to open ey
documentation it will say hey tools are
awesome it's a best tool for a job to
retrieve data from a system to enrich
your responses to make sure it's truth
and grounded but please use fewer than
20 functions to make sure you have a
good uh accuracy from uh our
experimentation or if you look at
Microsoft features we use around five
fiveish and we see pretty pretty good U
results so we would suggest you stay
around 5ish but obviously as a
technology improve as large language
model will improve probably the number
will grow over time and by the way we
have samples if you go to our B Tech you
can see a number of samples how to use
tools how to bring tools C pilot
extension we keep them up to date with
every release and every wave it's a
great great place to get started go
ahead and explore all
that using tools so using tools help y
pilot to deal with
fabrication in business Central AI
toolkit we support multiple function
calling small thing but
important our recommendation you try to
build very specific co-pilot you can
build a copilot to help our with user
pricing about other states but if you
want to build like a gut capil which can
help you with everything uh you probably
don't have enough technology for now H
to deal with it so you want to stay
humble and small
smaller because if you have too many
tools we just don't have enough reliable
technology and large language model not
really sure which one to call and it
just kind of can put your calot
extension uh off track a bit and from
our experience the magic number is
around five but again try it out
experiment see what works for
you over the last releases and this
release we have a number of great great
videos how to extend copilot in business
Central and how to build your own
copilot I hope this video was helpful
you have something to think about on
this journey and with that I wish you a
wonderful day